Why the long face?
I think I was
too nervous
No,
you did a great job
Thank you
for saying that
You know I helped you
so much today, right?
Yeah, that's why
I'm saying thank you
Is that all?
What do you mean?
You could say
more than that
For example…
"I'll buy you a coffee"
or "I'll treat you dinner"
"How about a drink?"…
Okay, got it
I'll treat you dinner
Keep your words
Tonight, okay?
I was gonna treat you
to a fancy dinner
Why did you want it
at home?
Well…
I just needed
some rest at home
I'm swamped these days
and I wanted some
alone time with you
Okay, please dig in
Thank you
You don't seem to visit
your family very often
I was raised
by my grandma
but she's not here
anymore now
Oh, I'm sorry
It's okay
It's been a long time
What about you, Hyesung?
I…
I don't really get along
with my parents
They always stayed
with me when shooting
so we often
had a falling-out
So none of us is
close to family, huh?
We should get along
with each other then